yessoftware.com 2014-04-04

# YesSoftware Privacy Policy

1\. Our Use of Your Information.  
We use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content, layout, and services. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs.  
We may also use your information to deliver information to you that is related to our products and services, such as new product announcements, updates, and communications relevant to your use of the Site. If you do not wish to receive these communications, you may have the ability to opt out on the preferences page.

2\. Our Disclosure of Your Information.  
We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.  
Legal Requests. YesSoftware cooperates with law enforcement inquires and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights. Therefore intellectual property and other rights owners, and local, state, federal and international law enforcement can request and may receive your personally identifiable information.

3\. Email This Site to a Friend Service.  
The terms applicable to the Email This Site to a Friend service apply to your use of that service. Without limiting the foregoing, you may not use the service to send spam.  
We do not use the email addresses you enter for any purpose other than to send your email. We do not rent or sell these email addresses. Indeed, we generally discard the email addresses at some point after they have been used to send your email.

4\. Other Information Collectors.  
Except as otherwise expressly discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are members of our system or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy customs and policies. Since YesSoftware does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy customs and policies of that third party. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

5\. Security.  
YesSoftware uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.
